How do I start?
The finished product can be saved in the comments and the video will be uploaded on the website.
Let's get started!
Let's get started today,
Liu Nian's livestream we talked about during the Spring Festival.
When you reply to the post of Liu Nian on WeChat official account,
you can get Oxu's DXF version.
So today we are going to make a doll with this little girl's board
First, we will import this DXF into our software
Then we will open its board
But here we do not copy
Because we don't have a place to match the doll's board
So we put it in the 3D window
First put it in the 3D window
Then we copy it
So we don't have to put the same board in the same way
Now we put the ear, the tail and the tail
After that, we select all the board
And copy it out
Then we copy it out
After that, we move this half of the board into the 3D window
So this doll's board is roughly arranged
Then we start to sew this board
I don't know if you have friends
To take this board
And then try to sew it yourself
Anyway, when I got it from Mr. Yan
I was a little confused
I don't even know what this board is
What is this?
There is no way
Because I rarely make dolls
This is also one of my attempts
There are some places
It may be difficult to find its direction when sewing in the 2D window
It can be sewn in 3D
In this way, it is easier to find its position
The premise is that your board is placed well
Then when you click, you should pay attention to it
And it is also the direction of the click
Because it will determine the direction of the sewing line
After sewing, we will sew its feet afterwards
Then we use this free-to-sew to sew it
After sewing, we use this free-to-sew to sew it
Then it's a sewing of his body
Then the belly
Then it's his butt
So basically the whole
Some details are sewn up
Finally, there is his belly and back
A sewing line above
Like the tail and ears and the cow's feet
We will do one of his details later
So we are now
Turn it back on
And then
Select our other panels
And then print it
You can hold it up
Of course
If you want to make it look better
You can reduce the particle diameter in advance
So that it is easy to see its shape
At the same time
It looks a little flat, right?
We have to add pressure to it
Pull up
Before adding pressure
Pay attention to these opposite panels
Turn it over
All are panels facing the outside
Then we do the same
Together with all the panels
Use a positive pressure
So that the cow
It will be normal
Fill it up
After that
Now
I'll freeze it up
Then give it
Plus one of his
Cow's feet and ears
First of all, do the ears
Here
Actually
When I was doing it
Turned over a car
I don't know if you guys
Have you found it now?
Did you find it?
I put the direction of his ear
Put it back
So now
It's his ear
The direction
Move back
After that
His ear
The placement of the fold
It needs to be adjusted again
After that
Give it to him
Make it smaller
On the other side
Also sew his ears
In this way
The shape of his ears
Will be more beautiful
At first
It's a bit like a pig's ear
I'm here
Reduce the particle diameter
Then
His internal line
Re-adjust to 180 degrees
In this way
His ears will be more
A little bit
Cuter
Then
Give it to him
Use the colon layer
Give him another layer
Then give him
Fill the ears
Here
The colon layer
Because he will have a floating line
Connect the internal line together
So the floating line needs to be deleted
Then
His ears
In this way
We don't use pressure
But with the impact thickness
Fill it up
Because
Use pressure
In some smaller places
The effect may not be so obvious
Then
His floating line
Also changed to the default
Custom angle
In this way
His connection
Will be relatively smooth
A little bit
Then
Here
I put his
Cow's feet
After making the ears
Make the cow's feet
Go up
The cow's feet
And the following
The method of the ear
Is the same
Just give him a colon layer
Make a double layer
Then
After making the double layer
Because he is also
A relatively small part
Then we can give him
Add a thickness
Conflict thickness
In this way
Push him up
Will be better than this pressure
The effect is better
I'm here
I want to give him the cow's feet
Adjust its shape
Here it will be easy to fall
It's crooked
Because of the force
Then I added a fixed point here
Set it up
Like now
Use a little bit later
A little bit of fabric
Can be solved
Now
We put this
The tail of the cow
Also added
In fact
The method is the same as this ear
And the cow's feet
Just
Because he is also
A relatively small part
So after using it
After that
Also use this
Conflict thickness
To push him up
First of all, it's the colon layer
Then give it to him
Hardening
After hardening
We can use this
Fixing needle
Stick to the tip of his tail
Then adjust the position of his tail
And its shape
Can go up a little bit
Then pull him up
Make him look better
A little flat
Then here
Well
I just talked about it
Like the previous
Add this conflict thickness to him
Then here
In fact, I also tried
Just say
If you add this thickness directly
Without pressure
He will
Without hardening
He said it was relatively flat
So
To make him look better
The place of the tail of the cow
Can be hardened
But the pointy place
Can not be hardened
In this case
He will
The pointy place
Will be a little bit old
It's the same as the one sold outside
The doll
Just the same
The place of the tail
It's usually a little bit
A little bit old
And now
I'm going to give him this cow
Make him a dress
It's done with a 3D pen tool
That's it
Use this
If you want to
Make this cow
Into an OBJ
And then
In the form of a virtual model
Fall in
Before that
It's like this now
All of it
This negative
It's the back to the outside
This black one
The board
Turn it all over
All become
This one
The front side of the board
To the outside
And then
Give him to move out
After that
You can choose
Our board
All frozen
And then
Use the document
Move
And then
Choose this one
For OBJ
One of his settings
It's a very important part
Is to
One of the boards
He
All of them
All his
So
All of its faces
I just talked about it
Put its panel back to the outside
That is, under the texture surface
Those gray panels
Select it
Then turn it over
Let all the panels
After its front facing out
Choose a little more
Choose all the panels
Then give it OBJ
When OBJ is set
Just like we are now
One of the settings you see on the map
Is to select it as a single target
And put all the panels
Choose this one to merge
Then choose this thin one
Then we can click OK
To pour it out
If you have friends
Still display black screen
You can try to refresh it
And see if it works
OK
This is the 3D line of the clothes
Press the Ctrl key is the curve point
Then the left button is the straight line
Those of you who have used Clue know
This is a habit of Clue
Then I will give it to him
Make this circle line
In this circle line, actually adjust its position
Just need to adjust half
Don't bend it too much
Because when we open it
Just save half
This can ensure that the clothes are symmetrical
Then draw the bottom line of the clothes
Press the Shift key
Can help you draw this vertical or horizontal line
Then the next
Is his sleeve
Draw a line with a 3D pen
Use the 3D pen tool
To adjust the point on the line
After adjusting
Now we draw the line on his belly
If he is a person
It should be the front middle line
Then draw his back middle line
Then it is his shoulder
And his side
Then we draw this
After drawing
We use the flatness of the panel
That tool
Choose the area of our panel
The area of these two panels
Then click on the car
Then these two panels
Will appear in our 2D window
In this side
I am more of a strong force
So I'm going to turn this board to the right
And then we're going to do it
I just did a little bit of a quick operation
You can go back and show it to everyone
This is also a very important operation
That's when the board comes out
When we're doing this clothing simulation
When adjusting
And the details of this little cow behind
You need to turn this little cow into a virtual model
Give him a fire
Just right-click on the little cow
Give him a virtual model of anti-fire
Otherwise, it may affect the effect of this simulation
After the anti-fire, it is equivalent to non-existence
Then hide it and that's it
And then I'm going to do a spread on his clothes
And his one correction
What about here?
We're going to give him a reference line first
And then on this board
Use this tool to generate a circular curve
Take it
And then we're going to give him a place on his sleeve to make it round
After the
We can use this editing board tool to adjust his sleeve shape
Let him and this reference line
The position of the original board line
Let him adjust it
Make this line rounder
The effect will be better
After that
We can choose this board
And then give him a
Select this delete reference line
Just put it as a reference line
Delete the reference line
This line is a little bit less
It doesn't look that much of an impact
And then we're going to spread it out in front of him
And then we're going to delete the extra dot here
And then we're going to spread it out
And then we're going to do this
As a simulation
He's going to wear this little cow on his body
And then we're going to reduce his particle strength to a minimum
It's easy to see his shape
And then I'm going to give him this circle
Then we can choose his circle line
And then in the attribute editor
You can see that I'm pointing at this place right now
It's the length of the 2D line
You can see the length of one of his panels
And then based on this length
To create a scripted panel
The width is what we just chose
This is the width of one of the panels
And then the height then we have 2.5 centimeters here
And then a vault for him
But here
Just don't use this toي
It's because the
Draw and then look at his length
And then the length of the panel
And then?
and then sew it up
When sewing, we also have to pay attention to the direction of the pattern
After adding the pattern to the pattern
give it a little adjustment
and then flatten it
If it is difficult to flatten, you can harden it
Just pull it a little
After that
we will add the pattern to the sleeve
The same method, look at this length first
and then sew it up
When sewing
we also have to pay attention to the corresponding position of the sleeve
Then we also change the pattern
and then
we can give it
and then give it another seam allowance
Let me see if everyone has any comments
Someone said
I don't really understand the difference between anti-activation and freezing
Here I will tell you
Frozen is actually equivalent to turning this pattern into a solid
It exists
But it won't change the shape because of the simulation
It will still have a conflict of calculation with other panels
If you turn it into a state of anti-activation
Then it is equivalent to this pattern does not exist
When modeling
Its shape will not change
It will not change
At the same time
It will not have a conflict of calculation with other panels
Let's continue to look back
What's next
I will give him a place in the pattern
Add a fabric to him
Then add a needle fabric to him
Then change the name of his fabric
In this way
It's convenient for us to look at the corresponding fabric later
Okay, what's next
What I'm doing now is a hat
Give him a hat
First of all
Give him a pattern of a hat
Then adjust the curve below it
Because the hat is usually a little bit curved below
And then here
Because I think it's a little small
So I slightly adjusted its size
Then I want to make a five-piece hat
So on this side
When I put it on
I put four out
Finally, there are five panels
Then set it together as a joint panel
In this way
The relationship between these five panels
Are a mutual relationship
Then our 3D window
Take these panels and take a good shot
Because there is no arrangement
So we are here
We can arrange it manually with the subscription ball
After arranging
It is recommended to sew it in the 3D window
Because if you sew it in 2D
I can't figure it out at once
May be wrong
Then print it
Print it
It's okay
Let him sew it together
Then we will move it to this
On the head of a small cow
Through this method
We are first to look at this hat
Does this cow match
Don't make the hat bigger
Or smaller
Now the hat is a little small
So let's reduce its particle diameter first
A little rounder
A little better
Easy to judge its shape
Then we will change the size of this panel
Change one here
The others will follow the connection
Then we can see
The curve line below it
A little bit not enough
So we can adjust it
According to the state of 3D
Adjust the panel in 2D
Then simulate
Now it's basically OK
Then below
Then the following
Give him to do the simulation
First of all
I am also a single machine
The line at the bottom of this panel
See its length of a line
Then here
You can find
For the link panel
We choose a line
It shows here
This is the length of a single panel
Instead of
The length of a line of all panels
So here
We have to calculate it
Our software
Actually has a calculator
I don't know if you know this function
Right click
You can see this calculator
Then we will
The length of this line
Input in
X5
equals 198
Click OK
Then this 198
Will automatically
Go into this
In the window of this width
Is in this column
Then we enter its height again
We do 4 cm wide
In this way
This panel is made
Then
We put this panel
Give it an extension
Here I am
Different
The distance of movement
To check
Different extension effects
In the end
I think this
The possible effect
Will be better
Then
Below
I am
This one
The panel of the cover
And this hat
Give it together
When sewing
It can also be
Sew in the 3D window
This
Let's put the panel first
Put it well
We use the line sewing tool
According to its position
One by one
Click
The direction is OK
Then
We sew it together
Below
We
That
The hat is frozen
Then
When the pattern is simulated
Will not affect it
Then when it is simulated
You can find
Now this pattern is
Is
It's
It's too
Can't hold it
In fact, this
There is a small point
Is its
One
The angle of the sewing line
The problem
Is that the sewing line
Is also angular
You can see
It hardens
It will have such an angle
Then I can choose
This sewing line
OK
Then in that
In the attribute editor
OK
Find this folding angle
From 180
A flat angle
Give it a bigger angle
OK
That way
It can hold up a little
OK
Even if I take it away
This head
It's the same
Will hold up
Now
I need to give it a position
Adjust
Let him wear this hat
It looks better
OK
Then give it a simulation
Is
Simulation
Then
Stop the simulation
Then move the position
A little bit
Take this hat
One
Position
Give it a good adjustment
Then after doing it
I'm in the middle of this hat
Give it a three-layer line
Then give it a column
This way
Can be made into that kind of double layer
Then add cotton effect in the middle
That kind of hat
Then here
After I disassembled the hardening
I found its shape
May be a little bit
It may be a little bit
It is not ideal
So
I will
Take it
That
Angle
Slightly
Adjusted
Then
Give it a hardening
Hold it up
Hold up the hardening below
Then don't harden the top
That way
It can keep this one
This kind of cotton
A little bit of a bone
The effect
Then freeze it
Then simulate the bottom
That way
Draw it up and down
There will be one
A little bit better
One
It is the effect of the bottom
And then
Next
We need to give it
Add a butterfly knot
On her clothes
This way
It will look
More
It is more
We use
A butterfly knot in the clothes
Quickly arrange
Put it on
And then use a fake needle
To set it
Many people
The first time
I knew
The angle of the curve line
It is also the first time
To know there is a calculator
You can find it in the common use class
Various kinds of magical things
Of course
Also pay attention to our live broadcast
Ha ha
And now
I'm going to
Take it out
And then
The position of its seam
To it
Go to it
Adjust it
Then simulate again
Then simulate it
So that
Its
The state of the butterfly knot
It's more
Cute
So that
It's more
Cute
The shape of the butterfly knot
Is more
Pretty
Next
And then
I'm going to
Hit it
It's
That's
This
Next
What do I give it
Then pull out its eyes
I want to copy it out
Then I just did a little operation
It's a little slow, sorry, it's slow
This little operation is very important
It's also a small function point
Because when I edit this glasses
Because it's on the top of our face
In the process of editing this glasses
It may accidentally move to the face of this glass
Then it's not good to change the version
So here I did a operation to lock it
Lock this version
After locking
Then I can easily change the glasses on it
Instead of worrying about changing the next one
Then we choose this version
Give it a link
Then do an external expansion of the version
Expand it by 1 mm
Then next
Make a cut for it
Or cut and sew
It doesn't matter here
Because the glasses are not part of the simulation
Then we put the mirror frame on it
Why do you have to put this whole mirror frame
It's so tight
One is because our glasses don't need to be sewn
So the between the panels
Don't need this gap
The other one
You can use such a 2D arrangement position
To make 3D glasses
It's also possible to do this
It's a better shape
It's just right
Let me take a look
Xiaoxi reminds me of some cute chats
Let me see what it is
This time, the material file of the cow's head
Is it the sharing of bragging?
No problem
This cow's head file
It can be shared with everyone
After we finish the live broadcast
You can put it in this public number
Open it up on the WeChat public number platform
When you reply to this designated language
You can get such a file like this
This is the file
Then we continue to look at the back
Then we have to lock it up
Then add a shortcut to it
Is it called a shortcut?
I don't know
Because Samasa has never worn glasses
I know this is a very hateful thing
Then we put this little one
What about the shortcut?
Draw it out for him
Then after drawing it out
Change its particle diameter to one
Because this is relatively small
If you don't change it to one
Its shape will not be very good
I want to give it a symmetrical spread
So that it is convenient for both sides of us
Make a change at the same time
And then we can use this
Editing curve tool
To slightly adjust this
This is a shape of the glasses
You can add some points
Make it look better
Because the main thing is that this version is relatively small
So when he draws it
Maybe you think it's not that smooth
Then you can add a little bit more
Make it better
Then we adjust it again
After this shortcut
Then we start to go in the 3D window
To deal with it
Then first select these panels
Then on the 3D window
Right click
Select reset 2D arrangement position
In this way
It can be placed in the same position as the 2D window
There is no need to move the positioning ball in the 3D window
Because of the movement of this positioning ball
Sometimes if you are not familiar with it
It can be easy to move bad
Then the glasses are not involved in the simulation
We just move it to this cow's head
Put it in place
Slightly adjusted
Adjusted well
Try to stick it to the cow's face
Don't make it hollow
It will be more real
Then after that
We can give it a gold frame
To the right place
To increase its thickness
Make it thicker
Then set its curve rate here
Change to 20
In this way
It will be cooler
It looks better
In this way
Our glasses are done here
So far
All the 3D things are done
Now
Let's start
One of its materials
A setting
First of all, the cow body
The cow's body
Here
Give it an application
A milk cow
A cream of milk
A cream of cream
This cream of cream
In fact, it is used in Clor
The cream of this cream
And then
Change it to a cream
A texture
Now
Put it in this position
Let's move it a little
Let the cow look better
The texture
The face mask is changed
And then
Next is its face
The face is also applied to it
A new fabric
To add a human hair
This is the kind of
This kind of fabric is often used in fur toys
Then include the layer under its ear
Inside
And the nostrils
Also apply this fabric
The name is also changed
Convenient to distinguish
Change its color to pink
And then the cow's feet
The cow's feet
Here I choose
One of the leather materials
And then
Next is the mirror
Mirror
How to do
In fact, it is
The chip
Sorry
Wrong
The chip is directly used
The material of this classic
And then
When it is on
It will become
This transparent effect
Because the glass
The glass
It is this transparent effect
it is here
I realized through the levelling
I found out his face
It's ugly
so
Here is the pattern
Changed it
a bit
then
Next
Go to our mirror
The mirror
Also for it
Choose this plate
Use a new fabric
Choose a metallic one here
här
To make
Aок
A yellow ц
That's good
a gold-colored glass
Next is the Butterfly Festival version
Select the version and click on the application
Then apply this grid material
Then add a little hair line
Make it more realistic
Then the next step is to modify the clothes
Here, the clothes are here
I deleted all the material pictures
Then apply a more realistic, more beautiful, and more obvious texture
The texture effect is more obvious
Because I am a needle fan
I really like the texture effect of this needle
So I also put on such a dress for this cow
Now I give it this cancel link
Then add an internal line to its middle line
Then turn it to the correct
Turn it to XO
Turn it to the right
Not XO
Turn its line of thought to the right
Because in this way
Its needle texture is the correct texture
Then give it a lot of color
Apply a yellow
Brown
A little deeper than brown
Such a color
Then add a sticker to it
Add this blind cute
Everyone is cute every day
Then move its position
Then change its color
From the pattern
Then use a brown
Then here I use the hair line to increase its embroidery effect
If you want the kind of light reflection
The kind of line with a stronger light reflection
You can change it to a shiny material
Now I am changing the name of the material that corresponds to it
Now the heavy head drama is coming
It's the place where the tail of the cow is cut
The tail of the cow
I'm going to make him a hair here
Make a hair
Then we are here
First apply a hair material to him
Then I choose here
On the basis of the material of fox hair
Make a change
There will be a lot of jade hair in our cloud
Everyone can make changes on this basis
Okay, let's click on the rendering
You can see it in the window of the rendering
There will be this one
This is a hair effect
It's a hair ball
Then we are going to modify its gravity
Make it look better
Then we come down and find gravity
First of all, because of this tail
Our current form
Its tail is forward
Then we are in the cloud
If it's forward, it's Z
If it's forward and backward, it's Z
Z go
So here I am going to do it
Make a adjustment in the direction of his Z
I'll give him a neutral one first
A direction of gravity
Then we can see it
This hair will go forward
The direction will go forward
Then I give him a positive value of X
Give him some positive
Make it a little bit more
Because this tail is a little bit
It's facing the front left
So I keep adjusting this one
A weight of X
Make it closer to him
This is the direction of the tail
Then the direction of the tail
It can be adjusted through this gravity
Because it's mainly before
There are a lot of children
Are asking us
Will ask this
What is the gravity of this hair?
That is mainly used here
That is when this hair
When the direction and your gravity
When the direction is not the same
It can be adjusted through this gravity
To adjust the direction of this hair
OK
Now
The direction of this hair
After getting it done
Next we are going to do this hair
Make some slight adjustments
So that he can achieve more
One of my ideal effects
It's a little bit curly
That kind of hair
Then I just
Turn off the hair behind him
This can save him
A calculation
That will make him show up
A little faster
When everyone is making clothes
If you say your clothes
There is no need for hair inside
Then you can put this fabric
This hair behind
Turn it off
Just use it
Change the same material
Turn off
Then choose the material of this mat
Just do it
OK
Then what about the following
We will do it to him
Length adjustment
OK
And then
One of his curls
A little bit
Let him slightly
That's a little bit
A little bit of that
Okay
It's just a hair
Just a little bit
This feeling
OK
This one
So it's done
Just a little bit curly
It's a little bit curly
The feeling of
Now
This hair
There is a problem
Is that it's too bright
Not quite in line with my heart
Ideal hair
So
I'm here
To his one
Lightness
It also has a
Lightness increase
And smoothness
Make some adjustments
Let's do it again
At this time, the fur is the effect I want
After this fur is done
Next, let's make this hat
When I was making the hat here
When I was preparing to adjust the material
I found a very fatal problem
I didn't adjust the hat
So you can pay attention to these small details
I fixed the needle here
Because after the hat is turned
The shape may need to be changed again
So I also gave the hat to him
And then here
I anti-activated the fur here
Because of the fur
Because of the cow's feet
He held the whole hat
So the shape just now is very good
It's not normal
Then I just put this hat on him
Anti-activate the plate and sewing line
That's equivalent to us
At the beginning
It's the same as when I didn't do the hat
At this time
The hat of the simulation
The shape will be a little better
Then we use this fixed needle
Just set it in the middle a little bit
Then simulate again
In this way
His shape will be more natural
Then freeze it again
Then give him the hat
To activate
That's the same as before
Just half of the board
Is hard for him
The other half is not hard
Then let him simulate it
Freeze it
Then the following board
Solve the hardening
Simulate again
Then this hat
This shape is adjusted
What's next
Give this hat
To make a material
First of all
Let's add a sticker to him
Add a little bear
A sticker
On this side
I originally wanted to make it a little bigger
Then
Make a cross-sectional effect
But I found this hat
When I was drawing this board
It's a little too big
So
It's a little bigger
That is, it's a little bigger
This one
The effect of the cross-sectional gap
Will not be ideal
So on this side
I didn't do this cross-sectional gap
And then
Put his color
Make a change
OK
Then
Change it to a brown
OK
I'll take a look
What's the chat
Can the sweater show
Is it a bit of a feather texture
OK
You can
The fabric of the sweater
Is also the same
Set it to a feather
A material
Then
Adjust the parameters inside
You can achieve this
A little bit of the effect
The sweater is a little bit
It's a little bit
A sweater
It's like that
I'm a sweater with a sweater
Or a sweater with a sweater
A sweater with a sweater
OK
What about us
There will be a period
I've been there before
A period of time
The teacher did a hair
A hair
Special theme live broadcast
OK
What about those who are interested
You can go back and take a look
A broadcast of this live broadcast
OK
Next
Give this hat
Applying a material
I didn't change the name for the time being because it didn't work
Because I forgot to re-apply this fabric
If you want to use the fabric
I have to change it again
Here I changed his name
After changing
Give him another color
I wanted to make him a little yellow hat
But I used a little yellow hat to add color
Then shrink it
I found out that the cow was too yellow
Not good
In order to balance his color
So I changed his yellow to a pink hat
That's also very cute
In the end
After we did this
Because at first we used a touch fabric
So the shape of the cow's feet and the cow's ears are not very good
So I'm here
Just give him
In this way
Do a molding on a molding
First of all, give him a fixed needle
Then grind it down
See if it's stable
It's still stable now
Because the fabric is a little hard
And then
He's still a little bit small
He's a little bit old
So he's still a little bit of a particle
The diameter is relatively large
For this cow's foot
Not very smooth
Then I will reduce its particle diameter here again
Become two
That's a lot of roundness
And then cancel the fixed needle again
At this time
I found it was still quite stable
And the shape of this cow's foot is also more natural and beautiful
And then the following is the cow's ear
Also the same
Give it a freeze
Then give him a simulation
At this time
The cow's ear has also become much more stable
In that case
The whole thing is done
And now we can simulate
But here
I also turned a car
Because when I simulated it
found
Oh my god
This is a cow with a white eye
I forgot to put my glasses on him
Because his glasses are there
You've been blocking me
So I forgot his existence
OK
So now I'm going to put his glasses on him
Hide him
Give him to put his glasses on
What about here
Conditional children
You can make one yourself
In the other 3D software
To model a ball-shaped eye
As a component
Add it up
Then apply this
Plastic material
Or plastic material
Plastic material or plastic material
Plastic material
In this case
Because I don't have this OVJ
So I'm directly on the board
The base window
To do it for him
First of all
Is to put the rest of the board
Give him to reactivate
Because he has nothing to do with this eye
Connection
You can give it to reactivate
In this case
It can make his calculation
Big reduction
It will make his simulation faster
And then
This board of his cow's ear
Just give him a freeze
Because the cow's face and this board
It's a direct contact when the board is good
Then we will give this eye
To make a set of the material
First of all
I'm here to confirm
This fabric one
This fabric
Only the eyes are used
Then give him
Changed his name
To make a material setting for him
First of all
Turn it into this plastic material
Is a material of plastic
Put its surface roughness on it
Change it to zero
In this way
It can achieve the smoothest material
Then turn its color into a black
Here and there
All the black ones
Do not recommend
Rgb000 black
Because of this
It will cause him
It's too black
This effect
It may not be so good
Then we will put this
Glass
Choose him
Put his particle diameter
Lower it a little bit more
In this case
This is the effect of this
It will be more smooth
Then give him to apply a very soft fabric
Is a real
A real fabric of silk
Very soft
You can see his gold tail sand
And the pressure of the pair of hands is very small
Be careful to remind me to see a
Let you have any misunderstandings
If it is made rough
Adjust it to a few
This surface roughness
A strength adjustment
Is based on your ideal
One of the effects
I just want to achieve this material effect
To be adjusted
If you want to be rough
Just put it on the side with a large number
To adjust
The smaller the number, the smoother it is
The bigger it is, the rougher it is
What exactly is it?
You have to look at your own
Effect
Look at 3D
To see what kind of effect you want
Let's make a adjustment
Then now
I'm going to put his pressure
Confirm that it is 30 pressure
Then give him a simulation
You can see it bulging up
Pressure is not enough
Let's adjust it to 70
At this time we can see this eye
It will bulge
It will bulge and be bright
Bling bling eyes
Bright eyes
Then I finally put it
A French line
A hair line wall
Adjust it to 0
So that it has no trace of the hair line
Will be more beautiful
Finally, I will show his glasses
Then do another smoothing
Finally, I will confirm its effect
Okay
Then our little cow
Kawaii Kawaii
A very cute little cow
It's done
Then here
After I finished
I'm still
Oh, I don't want to stop
Because he is too cute
So I'm here
Look inside and look again
Oh really
In self-appreciation
Do you know
Then
I thought of a small point here
Can share with you
There may be some children
You will also know such a small point
Is his picture
Then we default
A picture size of a picture
Let's say 640 x 480
This is a picture with the lowest clarity
Its rendering
The effect of the output is the fastest
Then use this
In fact, it can
Convenient to preview this rendering effect
Everyone is doing this
When the clothes
You can give him
Use this first to preview its effect
After you feel OK
You can adjust it to other sizes
For example, A4
Like this kind of cow
A doll like this
It's horizontal
Mainly its composition is horizontal
So you can put it
The direction of the picture becomes a horizontal
In this case, it can be as much as possible
Enlarge this cow's one
View
Then
It also makes the whole composition more harmonious
That's it
I basically have this
A live broadcast of this issue is complete
If you have any questions
You can post it in the chat
I can answer them for you
Let me take a look
Short legs are so cute
If your legs are short, they are not cute
I'm sorry
If it's a cow, the short legs are cute
Can it be made into a fur
Can be made into a fur
It can be made into a fur
Just make the material of the fabric into a fur
Then it is
Every time you open the 5.2 version of the sewing line
Will run
The sewing line will run out
Every time you want 3
In the default situation, the sewing line's hair line
Are all in a state of strength
Is the state of opening
Because of this
The clothes you made will have this sewing mark
If you don't want it
You can turn it off
The strength is 0, that's it
After sewing the glasses, it's no longer simulated, is it?
In fact
In fact, this simulation
Because the main thing is to make this doll now
There are more things in it
It's all about this kind of instant simulation
This cow is still
A little simpler
Oh my god, is the net broken again?
Oh no no no no no
OK, okay, okay, okay, the net is back
I'll continue to talk
Because it's mainly me
There will be a screen to monitor here
I just saw a black screen again, it scared me a little bit
Then after sewing the glasses, it's no longer simulated, is it?
This question
It's because when you're making dolls
Like
There are some places that may involve the control of this shape
Just a moment of simulation
After simulation
It's not moving anymore
That kind of
So sometimes when you add it
Don't let him participate in the simulation
Just like this glasses
If the glasses are simulated, it will fall down
So here
You can turn this glasses on
Give it back to life
In this case, it will not affect some of the conditions behind you
If you think
It's going to be a lot of trouble
How about
Then you can put this one
After the glasses version is done
Select it
Then block it as OBJ
Then import it again
Add it in the form of a copy
Just do it
In this case
You don't have to worry about it no matter how you simulate it